

# **DEJAN PETROVIC**Senior Front-End Developer



#### **EDUCATION**

#### 2013 - 2016

Bachelor's Degree, In Computer Science

Jilin Unviersity, China



#### SKILLS

React/React Native

Angular/Vue

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

Rest APIs

Bootstrap/Figma

MongoDB/MySql/PostgreSQL

Git/Docker

lest



#### CONTACT



✓ dejanpetrovickgy@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/dejanpetrovic-139b41246

**Yellow** Kraaljice Natalije 18, Belgrade



#### **PROFILE**

A frontend developer who is an expert in UI/UX development. For the past 6 years, have been designing and developing websites, using a keen eye for interactive design to develop pixel-perfect code that translates static design concepts into engaging digital experiences.

Main areas of focus are in HTML5/CSS3 (Sass), JavaScript and its frameworks and libraries including React.js, Vue.js, Angular.js.



#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Senior Front-End Developer

Evermore, Full time

Sep 2019 - Aug 2022

- Developed and maintained 20+ front-ends focused on user experience from scratch using React.js, Angular.js.
- Created and updated **6** websites with a focus on creating an exceptional user experience.
- Utilized and implemented **7**+ attractive, responsive, and mobile-friendly website contexts and elements using Vue.js, Node.js.
- Mentored 8 new junior front-end developers on team in expanding JavaScript, React and Angular skillset.

## Mid-Level Front-End Developer Mar 2018 - Aug 2019 Lucidity Company, Contract

- Collaborated with **3** engineering teams on domain, design and code testing for **15+** projects using React.js, Node.js, Vue.js.
- Wrote 35 automated tests to raise code quality as part of the development process using Jest.
- Followed industry best practices, company best practices to accomplish 100% of code/work

#### **Frontend Developer**

Sep 2016 - Feb 2018

PanonIT Company, Contract

- Designed a business locator for food businesses with 4+ star ratings.
- Experimented, explored and developed 13 new UI building blocks used to create smart, beautiful, enterprise-level software experiences.
- Created Mobile Responsive User Experience with CSS grids, learned new **3** technologies.